So do you use OBS to livestream,
or I mean use it on Sundays to
project? If you do, then this
app is going to be really,
really useful for you. It's on
Play Store. Don't worry, you can
send me a DM or comments down
below and I'll share you the
link to download it. It's an app
where you can control your OBS
app with ease. So I'm going to
switch to live screen, um, full
screen mode. So I get to see
this. So I get to see all my
scenes. If you notice, the
scenes here are the same as the
one here. So it lists all your
scenes. So currently I'm in MC
Presentation, and then we have 4
sources right now. I can hold
down the MC Presentation card
you get to see View Sources,
right? Can you see?
Do you know that I can
literally, from the app, I can
turn it off, turn it back on?
Can you see that? I can turn it
off, I can turn it back on. I
can drag sources around. So if
you notice, camera is the last
source there. I can literally
drag the camera source to
the top. Guess what happens now?
The camera source is at the top,
so I don't have to move my mouse
for anything. So imagine you
have a laptop that is not fast
or hangs a lot. You don't have
to literally move your mouse
every time. I can turn off the
camera source, and of course I
can delete it. Can you see that?
All in this mobile app.
So the other beautiful thing is
that I can literally, literally
control my audio. I can
literally control my audio,
literally, from the app. So I
can pause, I can restart,
pause, play,
I can restart. I mean, this is
beautiful. I can restart.
I can increase the volume. I can
probably reduce the volume. Can
you see that? So you watch,
right? Notice that the volume is
also reducing, reducing,
increasing. You know that I can
monitor and output. I can turn
off the monitoring, um, Um,
function. So when I click on
monitor off, notice what happens
when I click on monitor off. It
goes off from my phone. So I'm
using an Android emulator, do
you understand? So that you can
see both, um, both sides
of, um, the app. So I can pause
the audio. Guess what? It gets
paused. I can play the audio all
from my phone. You can literally
unmute your mic from your phone.
So watch, you see, I'm muting
and unmuting. So if you want to
have this beauty— and also I
forgot to mention, you have
access to a lot of quick
actions. So you can— okay, let
me click on Enable Studio Mode.
Guess what happens? It enables
studio mode all from your mobile
phone. Disable Studio Mode.
So if you want to enjoy this
beauty, send me a DM or a text
and I'll share it with you.